https://hikerwriter.com/hiker-writer/privacy-policy/

Sorry about the formal tone of this — My understanding is that Google won’t rate the site or index it without a privacy policy, so here it is…
What information do we collect?
You may visit our site anonymously and post comments anonymously.
When commenting on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you on your visits to this and other sites on the Internet. We have no access to this information.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website or link to other sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on 08/29/2011
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
KBerger466 at aol dot com
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *Comment Name *
Search for:
